Guide to the American Newspaper Repository Collection, 1852-2004 RL.10057
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Forward (New York), 1917-1975, 42
  - Forward (New York), 1944 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4210)
  - Forward (New York), 1944 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4207)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4205)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4202)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3818)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4203)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4204)
  - Forward (New York), 1945 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4201)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4199)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4200)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4195)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4196)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4197)
  - Forward (New York), 1946 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4198)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4194)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4193)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4189)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4192)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4190)
  - Forward (New York), 1947 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4191)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4188)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4184)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4185)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4186)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4183)
  - Forward (New York), 1948 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4187)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4239)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4241)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4243)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3819)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4240)
  - Forward (New York), 1949 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4242)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4238)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4236)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4233)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4235)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4234)
  - Forward (New York), 1950 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4237)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4229)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4231)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4232)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4230)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 4228)
  - Forward (New York), 1951 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4227)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4225)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3298)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 May-June; bound volume (Volume 4226)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3297)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3296)
  - Forward (New York), 1952 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4224)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3304)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3299)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3301)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3302)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3300)
  - Forward (New York), 1953 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3303)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3309)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3306)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3310)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3305)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3307)
  - Forward (New York), 1954 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3308)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3809)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3281)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3277)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3280)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3279)
  - Forward (New York), 1955 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3278)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3285)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3284)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3282)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3283)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3286)
  - Forward (New York), 1956 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3287)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3291)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3293)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3290)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3288)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3289)
  - Forward (New York), 1957 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3292)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3313)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3294)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3314)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3312)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3311)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 2609)
  - Forward (New York), 1958 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3295)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3336)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3316)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3335)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3337)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3315)
  - Forward (New York), 1959 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3338)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3344)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3345)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3328)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3320)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3327)
  - Forward (New York), 1960 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3317)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3325)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3319)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3340)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3350)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3326)
  - Forward (New York), 1961 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3351)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3324)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3331)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3339)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3334)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3352)
  - Forward (New York), 1962 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3343)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3342)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3330)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3333)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3323)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3346)
  - Forward (New York), 1963 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3349)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3318)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3347)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3321)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3341)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3329)
  - Forward (New York), 1964 Nov.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3354)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 3355)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 Mar.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3348)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 May-June; bound volume (Volume 3322)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3353)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 Sept.-Oct.; bound volume (Volume 3332)
  - Forward (New York), 1965 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 469)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 524)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 585)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 543)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 559)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 572)
  - Forward (New York), 1966 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 552)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 565)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 573)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 566)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 496)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 483)
  - Forward (New York), 1967 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 539)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 592)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 579)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 580)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 586)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 594)
  - Forward (New York), 1968 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 587)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 593)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 588)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 581)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 589)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 576)
  - Forward (New York), 1969 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 575)
    [Note: Missing Nov. 16]
  - Forward (New York), 1970 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 569)
  - Forward (New York), 1970 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 570)
  - Forward (New York), 1970 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 577)
  - Forward (New York), 1970 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 590)
  - Forward (New York), 1970 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 546)
    [Note: Missing Oct. 10]
  - Forward (New York), 1970 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 545)
  - Forward (New York), 1971 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 544)
  - Forward (New York), 1971 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 595)
    [Note: Missing Apr. 22]
  - Forward (New York), 1971 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 596)
  - Forward (New York), 1971 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 582)
  - Forward (New York), 1971 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 583)
  - Forward (New York), 1971 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 563)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 557)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 549)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 554)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 553)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 547)
  - Forward (New York), 1972 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 555)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 598)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 591)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 584)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1617)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 574)
  - Forward (New York), 1973 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 567)
    [Note: Missing Nov. 6]
  - Forward (New York), 1974 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 561)
  - Forward (New York), 1974 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 568)
  - Forward (New York), 1974 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 562)
    [Note: Missing June 2, 7]
  - Forward (New York), 1974 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 556)
    [Note: Missing Aug. 4-10]
  - Forward (New York), 1974 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 548)
  - Forward (New York), 1974 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 597)
  - Forward (New York), 1975 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 578)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 4, Feb. 21]
  - Forward (New York), 1975 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 564)
    [Note: Missing Apr. 12]
  - Forward (New York), 1975 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 571)
- France Amerique (New York), 1943-1953, 43
  - France Amerique (New York), 1943 May 23-1944 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1141)
  - France Amerique (New York), 1945 Jan. - 1945 Aug. 12; wrapped bundle (Box 1140)
  - France Amerique (New York), 1946 Mar. 19 - 1946 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1140)
  - France Amerique (New York), 1947; wrapped bundle (Box 1139)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 15, Dec. 14]
  - France Amerique (New York), 1948 Sept. 12-Dec. 26; wrapped bundle (Box 453)
    [Note: Missing Oct. 3, 17, 24; Dec. 5]
  - France Amerique (New York), 1949 Feb. 13 - 1949 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 453)
    [Note: Missing Apr. 13, Aug. 7, Sept. 11, Nov. 20]
  - France Amerique (New York), 1950; wrapped bundle (Box 1138)
  - France Amerique (New York), 1951; wrapped bundle (Box 1137)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 21; Feb. 11, 18; Mar. 18; Apr. 29; Aug. 19, 26; Sept. 30]
  - France Amerique (New York), 1952; wrapped bundle (Box 1143)
  - France Amerique (New York), 1953 Mar.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1142)
- Gaelic American, 1916-1919, 44
  - Gaelic American, 1916 Sept.-1917 Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3138)
  - Gaelic American, 1918 Jan.-1919 May; bound volume (Volume 3139)
- Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1880-1901, 45
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1880 Mar. - 1880 Dec. 4; wrapped bundle (Box 1193)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1880 Dec. 11-1881 Dec. 3; wrapped bundle (Box 1194)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1882; bound volume (Volume 5911)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1882 Dec.-1883 Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5915)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1883 Dec.-1884 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5930)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1884 Dec. 6-1885 Dec. 5; wrapped bundle (Box 1195)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1886 Apr.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1189)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1886 Dec.-1887 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5920)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1887 Dec.-1888 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5940)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1888 Dec.-1889 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5929)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1889 Nov.-1890 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5947)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1890 Nov.-1891 Nov; bound volume (Volume 5946)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1891 Nov.-1892 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5939)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1892 Nov.-1893 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5977)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1893 Nov.-1894 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5948)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1894 Nov.-1895 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5921)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1895 Nov.-1896 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5931)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1896 Nov.-1897 Nov; bound volume (Volume 5914)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1899 Nov.-1900 Nov.; bound volume (Volume 5938)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1900 Nov. 17-1901 Nov. 9; wrapped bundle (Box 1201)
  - Golden Days (Philadelphia), 1901 Nov. 16-1902 Nov. 8; wrapped bundle (Box 1192)
- Hairenik (Boston), 1946-1953, 46
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1946 July 18-Dec. 26; wrapped bundle (Box 500)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1947; wrapped bundle (Box 500)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1948; wrapped bundle (Box 530)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1949; wrapped bundle (Box 515)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1950; wrapped bundle (Box 516)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1951; wrapped bundle (Box 488)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1952; wrapped bundle (Box 490)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1953 Jan. 1-Nov. 12; wrapped bundle (Box 489)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1953 Nov. 19-Dec. 31; wrapped bundle (Box 489)
  - Hairenik (Boston), 1954; wrapped bundle (Box 501)
- Indépendence, 1896-1897, 47
  - Indépendence, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
- International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1954, 1962, 1965-1967, 1969-1970, 1976, 48
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1954 Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1749)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1962 Jan.; wrapped bundle (Box 202)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1965 Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1643)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1966 July; wrapped bundle (Box 1626)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967; wrapped bundle (Box 1750)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967 Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1642)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967 Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1638)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967 June; wrapped bundle (Box 1616)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967 Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1349)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1967 Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1350)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1969 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1344)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1969 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1341)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1969 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1345)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1969 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1346)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1970 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1342)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1970 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1343)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1970 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1347)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1970 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1348)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1976 Jan. 2-Mar. 28; wrapped bundle (Box 1786)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1976 Apr. 1- Sept. 27; wrapped bundle (Box 560)
  - International Herald Tribune (Paris), 1976 Oct. 22-Dec. 31; wrapped bundle (Box 1729)
- Intransigeant, 1896-1898, 49
  - Intransigeant, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
  - Intransigeant, 1897 Oct.-1898 Mar.; volume in box (Box 1690)
- Irish World (New York), 1880-1946, 50
  - Irish World (New York), 1880-1881; bound volume (Volume 3130)
  - Irish World (New York), 1882 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 3132)
  - Irish World (New York), 1882-1883; bound volume (Volume 3131)
  - Irish World (New York), 1884-1885; bound volume (Volume 3133)
  - Irish World (New York), 1885 Apr.-Dec; bound volume (Volume 3132)
  - Irish World (New York), 1886-1887; bound volume (Volume 3134)
  - Irish World (New York), 1888 Oct -1890 Dec; bound volume (Volume 3135)
  - Irish World (New York), 1891- 1892; bound volume (Volume 3124)
  - Irish World (New York), 1893-1894; bound volume (Volume 3125)
  - Irish World (New York), 1895-1896; bound volume (Volume 3126)
  - Irish World (New York), 1897-1898; bound volume (Volume 3127)
  - Irish World (New York), 1899; bound volume (Volume 3129)
  - Irish World (New York), 1900; bound volume (Volume 3128)
  - Irish World (New York), 1901; bound volume (Volume 3114)
  - Irish World (New York), 1902; bound volume (Volume 3115)
  - Irish World (New York), 1903; bound volume (Volume 3116)
  - Irish World (New York), 1904; bound volume (Volume 3117)
  - Irish World (New York), 1905; bound volume (Volume 3118)
  - Irish World (New York), 1906; bound volume (Volume 3123)
  - Irish World (New York), 1907; bound volume (Volume 3119)
  - Irish World (New York), 1908; bound volume (Volume 3120)
  - Irish World (New York), 1909; bound volume (Volume 3121)
  - Irish World (New York), 1910; bound volume (Volume 3122)
  - Irish World (New York), 1911; bound volume (Volume 5463)
  - Irish World (New York), 1912; bound volume (Volume 5464)
  - Irish World (New York), 1913; bound volume (Volume 5468)
  - Irish World (New York), 1914; bound volume (Volume 5470)
  - Irish World (New York), 1915; bound volume (Volume 5469)
  - Irish World (New York), 1916; bound volume (Volume 5471)
  - Irish World (New York), 1917; bound volume (Volume 5472)
  - Irish World (New York), 1918; bound volume (Volume 5473)
  - Irish World (New York), 1919; bound volume (Volume 5475)
  - Irish World (New York), 1920; bound volume (Volume 5474)
  - Irish World (New York), 1921; bound volume (Volume 5461)
  - Irish World (New York), 1922; bound volume (Volume 5462)
  - Irish World (New York), 1924; bound volume (Volume 5466)
  - Irish World (New York), 1925; bound volume (Volume 5465)
  - Irish World (New York), 1925; bound volume (Volume 5467)
  - Irish World (New York), 1926; wrapped bundle (Box 1103)
  - Irish World (New York), 1927; wrapped bundle (Box 1109)
  - Irish World (New York), 1928; wrapped bundle (Box 1108)
  - Irish World (New York), 1929; wrapped bundle (Box 1105)
  - Irish World (New York), 1930; wrapped bundle (Box 1101)
  - Irish World (New York), 1931; wrapped bundle (Box 822)
  - Irish World (New York), 1932; wrapped bundle (Box 814)
  - Irish World (New York), 1933; wrapped bundle (Box 815)
  - Irish World (New York), 1934; wrapped bundle (Box 823)
  - Irish World (New York), 1935; wrapped bundle (Box 826)
  - Irish World (New York), 1936; wrapped bundle (Box 816)
  - Irish World (New York), 1937; wrapped bundle (Box 829)
  - Irish World (New York), 1938; wrapped bundle (Box 830)
  - Irish World (New York), 1939; wrapped bundle (Box 824)
  - Irish World (New York), 1940; wrapped bundle (Box 809)
  - Irish World (New York), 1941; wrapped bundle (Box 1111)
  - Irish World (New York), 1942; wrapped bundle (Box 1104)
    [Note: Incomplete]
  - Irish World (New York), 1943; wrapped bundle (Box 1102)
  - Irish World (New York), 1944; wrapped bundle (Box 1107)
  - Irish World (New York), [1945]; wrapped bundle (Box 1110)
  - Irish World (New York), [1946]; wrapped bundle (Box 1106)
- Katolik (Chicago), 1961-1973, 51
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1961 Aug. 18- 1962 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1270)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1963; wrapped bundle (Box 1279)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1964 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1277)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1965; wrapped bundle (Box 1278)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1966; wrapped bundle (Box 1271)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1967; wrapped bundle (Box 1272)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1968; wrapped bundle (Box 1273)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1969; wrapped bundle (Box 1275)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1970; wrapped bundle (Box 1276)
    [Note: Missing Dec. 5-11]
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1971; wrapped bundle (Box 1274)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1972; wrapped bundle (Box 1268)
  - Katolik (Chicago), 1973; wrapped bundle (Box 1269)
- Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1949-1955, 1961-1965, 1968, 52
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1949-1951; wrapped bundle (Box 61)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1952; wrapped bundle (Box 48)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1953; wrapped bundle (Box 49)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1954; wrapped bundle (Box 35)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1955 Apr. 24-July 31; wrapped bundle (Box 50)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1961 Aug.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 47)
    [Note: Missing Nov. 26]
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1962 Jan.-July; wrapped bundle (Box 57)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1963 Feb. 10; wrapped bundle (Box 58)
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1964 Feb.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 59)
    [Note: Missing July 9]
  - Katolikus Magyarok Vasarnapja (Cleveland, Youngstown, OH), 1964 May-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 58)